

Samer BAHRI

Budapest/Hungary +36 20 433 6216 samer.bahri@ieee.org

github | in linkedin

SUMMARY

I am a Tunisian DevOps Engineer based in Hungary, with 3 years of experience specializing in platform engineering, MLOps, cloud, and DevOps practices. I hold a BSc in Software Engineering from the Budapest University of Technology and Economics. Passionate about innovation, I actively engage in homelabbing and open-source contributions to refine my skills and explore emerging technologies.

EXPERIENCE

DEVOPS ENGINEER | ERICSSON

2023-Current/ Hungary

- Handled responsabilities related to Kubernetes, CI/CD and Cloud Object Storage (MinIO S3) for Packet Core and Application Development Platform
- Took over responsabilities related to a Kubernetes microservice architecture, design and implementation details
- Refactored the testing framework for a Kubernetes microservice

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN | CONTINENTAL AG

2022-2023 / Hungary

- Implemented features and bug fixes as well as CI/CD for an internal web application (abstraction over kubernetes)
- Took part in Infrastructure and DevOps/MLOps improvements for the AI training cluster

CUSTOMER CARE INTERN | SUEZ

2019-2020 / Hungary

- Handled SalesForce and SAP customer success cases
- automated invoice email sending with python

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

BSC IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

January 2023

BUDAPEST UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND ECONOMICS

CERTIFIED KUBERNETES APPLICATION DEVELOPER (CKAD)

October 2023

THE LINUX FOUNDATION

FUNDAMENTALS OF DEEP LEARNING

April 2022

Nvidia

SKILLS ___

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES Python | Typescript | Javascript | Go

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT Bash | GIT | GitHub | Jenkins | GNU Make | pnpm | vite

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES React | Express | Flask | Robot Framework | Pytest | Tensorflow

CLOUD TECHNOLOGIES Docker | Kubernetes | Helm | AWS | Terraform | Ansible

SOFT SKILLS Project Management | Cross-team coordination | Agile Methodologies | Conducting Presentations

LANGUAGES Native: Arabic Fluent: English, French Beginner: Swedish

EXTRA

- Nulla et lectus vestibulum urna fringilla ultrices. Phasellus eu tellus sit amet tortor gravida placerat.
- · Nulla et lectus vestibulum urna fringilla ultrices. Phasellus eu tellus sit amet tortor gravida placerat.
- Integer sapien est, iaculis in, pretium quis, viverra ac, nunc. Praesent eget sem vel leo ultrices bibendum.

December 15, 2024 / source code